Guide to the Records of the Office of the President/Office of the Chancellor, New York University RG.3.0.6
New York University Archives
- Series I: Records
  - Medical Center: Post Graduate Medical School History, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center: School of Nursing, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center: School of Nursing, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Middle States Associaton: General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Middle States Associaton: General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Modern Language Association, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - New York City: Certificate of Business Merit to NYU, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - New York City: Services Rendered By, for NYU, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - New York State: Committee on Higher Education, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - New York State: State Education Dept., Research Committee, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - New York State: State Education Dept., State Advisory Council, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - New York State: University of the State of New York, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - New York University Press, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Nurse Education At NYU, Study of, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Oath of Allegiance, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Officer's Group, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Personnel Division: Office of the President, Data on Staff, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Division: Office of the President, Petitions on Holiday Curtailment, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Division: Procedures, Policy, and Memoranda, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Plant and Properties: Cooper Union, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Plant and Properties: Housing, Weinstein Hall, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Plant and Properties: Labor Relations, 1958-Jul 1959 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Plant and Properties: Labor Relations, Aug 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Plant and Properties: Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Plant and Properties: Washington Square Southeast Project, Extra-University Statements, 1953-Jan 1954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Plant and Properties: Washington Square Southeast Project, Extra-University Statements, Apr 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Plant and Properties: Washington Square Southeast Project, General Correspondence, 1952-Oct 1953 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Plant and Properties: Washington Square Southeast Project, General Correspondence, Nov 1953-Apr 1954 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Plant and Properties: Washington Square Southeast Project, General Correspondence, May 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Plant and Properties: Washington Square Southeast Project, Press Clippings, 1953-Jan 1954 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Plant and Properties: Washington Square Southeast Project, Press Clippings, Feb 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Plant and Properties: Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center, Publications, 1951-1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Policy Statements, 1953-1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Portraits of Former Chancellors, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - President's Committee on Education Beyond the High School: General Correspondence, 1956-Apr 1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - President's Committee on Education Beyond the High School: General Correspondence, May 1957-Nov 1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - President's Committee on Education Beyond the High School: Handbook, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - President's Idea Group, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - President/Chancellor's Office: Assistant to the President, General Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - President/Chancellor's Office: Correspondence Files, Location of, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - President/Chancellor's Office:General Correspondence File C, 1947-1955, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - President/Chancellor's Office: General Correspondence File E, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - President/Chancellor's Office: General Correspondence File M, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - President/Chancellor's Office: General Correspondence File R, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - President/Chancellor's Office: General Correspondence File S, 1951, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - President's Office Mailing List, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Provost's Office: Memoranda, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Provost's Office: Memoranda, May 1951 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Provost's Office: Memoranda, Jun 1951 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Provost's Office: Memoranda, Aug 1951 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Public Occasions, Bureau of, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Radio and Television: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Registrar, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Rehabilitation Services, Center for: General Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Rehabilitation Services, Center for: General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Religious Activities:Catholic Center, 1957-1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Report on Appraisal of Internal Control, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Reserve Officer's Training Corps (ROTC), 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Retailing, School of, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Secretary and Vice-Chancellor, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Self-Study, Report of Committee on, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Senate, University: Committee, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Senate, University: Elected Members Group, 1962-May 1964 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Senate, University: Elected Members Group, Oct 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Senate, University: Rights and Responsibilities of Faculty, 1951-1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Student Activities: Academic Freedom and Off-Campus Freedom, 1952-1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Student Activities: All-Square Student Leadership Conference, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Student Activities: Federation of Undergraduate Student Councils, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Student Activities: General Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Students, Dean of: General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Students, Dean of: General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Student Federation, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Student Health Services, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Task Force Operation, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - United Nations, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - United States: Peace Corps, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - University College of Arts and Science: Visiting Committee, 1954-1960 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - University Council: On Education for Public Responsibility, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - University Council: Special Committee to Make Nominations for Chancellor, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - University Valley: General Correspondence, 1960-Jan 1961 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - University Valley: General Correspondence, Feb 1961-Sep 1961 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - University Valley: General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Vice-President, Executive: Chart of Organization, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Vice-President, Executive: General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Vice-President, Executive: General Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Vice-President, Executive: General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square College: Dean's View, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square College: Faculty Communication, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square College: New General Program, Final Report, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square College: Advisory Comm. and Comm. Ed. Policy, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square College: Press Release, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square College: Proposal for Closed-Circuit TV Experiment, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Washington Square College: Visiting Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square Park Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - White House Conference on Education, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)